The ranger delves unusually deep in arts of destruction gaining a questionable reputation among the forest inhabitants. The hero learns Basic Destructive Magic, a random destructive spell and will suffer a -1 penalty to morale permanently. The Imbue Arrow ability will now affect Ballista as well. All Ballista shots will carry the hero's enchantments, and therefore drain his/her Mana. The hero loses his initiative whenever the imbued ballista acts.<color_default><br>
If the hero does not have at least 2 skillslots open destructive magic isn't learned and no morale penalty is applied. It is possible the hero learns no new spell if he already has the random choice. If Destructive Magic is unlearned with a mentor the morale penalty is also removed.