Class: Overlord<br>Specialization: Lizard Breeder<br><br><body_bright>Lizard Bite deals more damage, depending on hero level. Damage from Lizard Bite is 1.20+0.01*Level times the regular damage (instead of 0.5). Furthermore at the start of each week additional Dark Raiders, Grim Raiders or Brisk Raiders will join the heroes army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 0.13*Hero Level. No extra creatures will join before level 4. <br><color_default>The player can choose the type of creatures by placing the desired type in an army slot more to the left of the other types (only applicable if multiple types exist in the army).