Class: Demon Lord<br>Specialization: Imp Breeder<br><br><body_bright>At the start of each week additional Imps, Familiars or Quasits will join the heroes army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 0.9*Hero Level. <br><color_default>The player can choose the type of creatures by placing the desired type in an army slot more to the left of the other types (only applicable if multiple types exist in the army). The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.