Class: Häuptling<br>Specialization: Goblin King<br><br><body_bright>The number of Goblins in the hero's army increases weekly by an amount equal to the hero's level. The joining goblins will not be upgraded unless there already are upgraded Goblins in the army, and all upgraded Goblins will be joined by Goblin Trappers. Also, the Goblin’s chance to betray the hero will be reduced by 1% per hero level.