The hero becomes able to enhance his or her arrows with spells and learns a random Dark Magic spell from level 1-3. The imbued arrows will drain the hero's Mana.<br><color_default>Imbue Arrow lasts till the end of the combat or until all Mana is drained. Only one spell can be imbued at a time. The hero spends no ATB value to choose the imbuing spell, and can act again right away. It is possible the hero learns no new spell if he already has the random choice.