Every week the hero receives an amount of Sulphur equal to his Knowledge/2.<br><br><color=purple>Cornucopia (1/6)<color=white><br>Collect one artifact for every resource type (except gold) and visit an Arcane Library for a unique reward.<br><br><color=orange>Quest<color=white><br>Offer this artifact to a Temple of Shalassa and it will summon a stack of Fire elementals. The size of the stack is equal to 4*amount of weeks passed.<br><br><color=yellow>Backpack<color=white><br>This artifact works from the backpack, but functionality is limited to one artifact per resource type per hero.