The hero receives +1 Spellpower for every 7 experience levels, including the levels already gained. The Spellpower bonus is doubled if the hero does not learn Destructive Magic. The hero will also inflict 40% of normal spell damage against otherwise resistant creatures.<br><color_default>The irresistable effect works against luck based resistance, magic proof and immunities, but only for damaging spells, mind immunities cannot be overruled. Against 75% magic proof (example), the spell damage will become 25% + (40% of the remaining 75%) = 55%.