Links the hero with a selected creature in his army. Every time this creature performs an attack, the hero will assault the same target.<br><color_default>If the linked creature uses a ranged attack, the hero delivers his usual attack. If it uses a melee attack, the hero delivers an attack as if he was 3 levels higher. The hero also has an additional 10% chance to deliver a critical blow dealing double damage (giving 80% with Martial Arts, and 10% without). The hero spends only half a turn to place the link.