-------------------------------------------------------------------------------
ADVANCED RMG DUEL MAP
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------

1.Visit one Abandoned Mine to receive a random stash of Artifacts.
2.Visit one Witch Hut to receive a huge boost in experience.
3.Walk back to your town to make sure you learned all spells, buy all troops and don't forget the war machines!
4.Proceed to the middle zone to beat your opponent, your opponent should agree to fight on the random generated terrain type.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------
RULES
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------

-If your hero dies you lose the game, you cannot hire another one.
-To prevent players stalling the game, towns will be destroyed on day 8, after that you have a maximum of 7 days left to kill your enemy.
-Redwood Observatories on this map can restore your mana, other temporary boosters are not usable.
-The battle sites on this map are too dangerous on default setting and visiting them will cause you to lose.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------
BALANCE INFO
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------

-Town dwellings have some extra growth if a special faction building exists and dungeon tier1-3 has more growth to replace recruitment/ritual pit.
-Heroes with creature growth or dragonblood specializations will receive an extra stack of these creatures. 
-Heroes with resource specializations receive an extra stack of tier 7 creatures.
-Heroes with logistics specializations receive an extra stack of elementals.
-Necropolis heroes get an extra stack of skeletons, ghosts or wights depending on class.
-Wizards receive +4 Attack and +4 Defense, but cannot use the Arcane Forge.
-Rangers receive an extra stack of Blade Dancers, but cannot use the Avengers Guild.
-The army size, artifacts and experience are user-configurable settings in data/MMH55-settings.pak, if desired the game can be changed in a run for the battle sites, reducing the artifact stash and the neutral guards.