A quantity of native Tier1 creatures will be resurrected after combat, the amount of resurrected creatures is equal to 30% + 1% per Knowledge of the Hero. The resurrection costs 6 mana. No resurrection will take place if no mana is available. Undead, mechanical and elemental creatures cannot be resurrected.<br><br><color=purple>Garments of the Saint (1/5)<color=white><br>Mana cost of resurrection will be reduced by -2 per item if the hero carries at least 3 Garments of the Saint.