The hero will raise some of the fallen undead creatures in his/her army after combat. All necropolis heroes also raise an additional amount of skeletons after level 20, every week. The amount is equal to their Knowledge.<br><color_default>After every fight one stack having suffered a loss is randomly selected. Dead units in this stack are raised again, up to 7 + 5*(Hero Level) Hit Points, rounded down. 