Additional Spellcasters will join the hero's army every week. The number of Spellcasters is equal to Rounded(multiplier*hero knowledge), in which the multiplier = 0.17/0.25/0.33/0.42 based on the weekly growth of the spellcaster.<br><color_default>The amount can be zero if the hero level is too low. The type of Spellcasters depends on the faction of the hero and the ones present in his army; if there are none, no new ones of that type will join. The following (including upgrades) are considered as Spellcasters: Priests, Druideen, Pit Fiends, Liches, Mages, Runepriests, Shadow Witches & Shamans.