<color_bright>Allows a visiting hero to learn the spells kept within. Adds 3 spells of the third circle.<br><br>
<color=orange>Manticores<color_default><br>This building can summon Manticores and add them to the town garrison every week. The amount of summoned Manticores depends on the amount of Dragonblood crystals heroes have collected (A) and the experience level of those heroes (B). Formula = sum(A*B/500) * (1+Guild level). The amount is zero if no crystals are collected.<br><br>
<color=0099FF>Governance<color_default><br>Grants the Governor of this town a +3 Spellpower Bonus.