Grants the hero the ability to tie his or her own spirit to the spirits of any creatures on the battlefield until the end of combat. If linked creatures receive any damage, the hero will gain some Mana, feeding upon those creatures' suffering.<br><color_default>The hero restores 1 mana for every 50 damage received. Only one creature can be linked at a time. The hero spends only half a turn to choose a target.