The hero receives a special combat ability to consume corpses of fallen creature stacks to restore Mana. Consumed corpses disappear from the battlefield.<br><color_default>The hero restores 1 mana for every 40 Hit Points consumed. The hero’s maximum Mana cannot be exceeded. If the hero also has the Cultmaster perk, corpses will explode when they are consumed. The explosion will be the same as a Fireball spell cast by the hero; effective Spellpower is 1 if the consumed stack was not upgraded, and 2 if it was.