Grants the hero +1 Spellpower, the "Banish" ability and cuts down on enemy Summoning spell efficiency. The Summon Elementals spell summons only half of the Elementals, the conjured Phoenix, Blade Barrier and Hive have only half of their usual Hit Points.<br><br><color=orange>Quest<color=white><br>Offer this artifact to a Temple of Shalassa and it will summon a stack of Manticores. The size of the stack is equal to 2*amount of weeks passed.