Class: Necromancer<br>Specialization: Chosen of Asha<br><br><body_bright>At the start of each week additional Bone Dragons, Shadow Dragons or Ghost Dragons will join the heroes army. The amount is equal to 1 at level 12 and 2 at level 26. <br><color_default>The player can choose the type of creatures by placing the desired type in an army slot more to the left of the other types (only applicable if multiple types exist in the army). The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.